Preliminary Guide to the Corcoran Gallery of Art and Corcoran College of Art + Design, Corcoran Gallery of Art archives department records, circa 1890-2007 COR0005.3.RG
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- National Gallery of Art transfer, Series 7
  - Senator William A. Clark Collection Photos and Color Reproductions, undated; Series 7 (Box 117, Folder 5)
  - Clark Collection, undated; Series 7 (Box 117, Folder 6)
  - William Andrew Clark Art Collection, undated; Series 7 (Box 117, Folder 7)
  - Copies of Press Clippings Relating to Clark Bequest - Originals in PDS, undated; Series 7 (Box 117, Folder 8)
  - Clark Collection Information From Knoedler, undated; Series 7 (Box 117, Folder 9)
  - Clark Collection: Jacques Seligmann, undated; Series 7 (Box 117, Folder 10)
  - Senator William A. Clark Family Bios. Katherine (Stauffer) Clark, undated; Series 7 (Box 117, Folder 11)
  - Senator William A. Clark Family Bios. Family Tree, undated; Series 7 (Box 117, Folder 12)
  - Senator William A. Clark Family Bios. Senator William A. Clark, undated; Series 7 (Box 117, Folder 13)
  - Senator William A. Clark Family Bios. Senator William A. Clark Obituaries, undated; Series 7 (Box 117, Folder 14)
  - Senator William A. Clark Family Bios. Senator William A. Clark Will and Press, undated; Series 7 (Box 117, Folder 15)
  - Senator William A. Clark Family Bios. Senator William A. Clark Legal Battle of False Heirs, undated; Series 7 (Box 117, Folder 16)
  - Senator William A. Clark Family Bios. Anna (La Chapelle) Clark, undated; Series 7 (Box 117, Folder 17)
  - Senator William A. Clark Family Bios. William A. Clark, Jr., undated; Series 7 (Box 117, Folder 18)
  - Senator William A. Clark Family Bios. George John Pale, undated; Series 7 (Box 117, Folder 19)
  - Senator William A. Clark Family Bios. Huguette Clark, undated; Series 7 (Box 117, Folder 20)
  - Senator William A. Clark Family Bios. Huguette Clark Confidential/Giving & Proposals, undated; Series 7 (Box 117, Folder 21)
  - Senator William A. Clark Family Bios. Huguette Clark Confidential/Paintings in Personal Collection, undated; Series 7 (Box 117, Folder 22)
  - Senator William A. Clark Family Bios. Lewis Morris Hall, undated; Series 7 (Box 117, Folder 23)
  - Senator William A. Clark Family Bios. Amanda E. Clark, undated; Series 7 (Box 117, Folder 24)
  - Senator William A. Clark Family Bios. Misc. Descendents, undated; Series 7 (Box 117, Folder 25)
  - Clark Family Anna E. L. Clark, undated; Series 7 (Box 117, Folder 26)
  - Clark Family William Andrews Clark Jr., undated; Series 7 (Box 117, Folder 27)
  - Clark Family Katherine C. Clark (Hall), undated; Series 7 (Box 117, Folder 28)
  - Clark Family Charles Walker Clark (Baeyens), undated; Series 7 (Box 117, Folder 29)
  - Clark Family Mary Joaquino Clark, undated; Series 7 (Box 117, Folder 30)
  - Clark Family J.R. Clark (James Ross), undated; Series 7 (Box 117, Folder 31)
  - Clark Family Hughuette Clark, undated; Series 7 (Box 117, Folder 32)
  - Clark Family Elizabeth Clark Abascal, undated; Series 7 (Box 117, Folder 33)
  - Clark Family Paul Clark Newell, Jr, undated; Series 7 (Box 117, Folder 34)
  - William Andrew Clark Jerome + Clarkdale, undated; Series 7 (Box 117, Folder 35)
  - William Andrew Clark MSS Collections, undated; Series 7 (Box 117, Folder 36)
  - William Andrew Clark Will and Woodlawn Cem., undated; Series 7 (Box 117, Folder 37)
  - William Andrew Clark Other Benefactions, undated; Series 7 (Box 118, Folder 1)
  - Senator William A. Clark Family Bios Archival Document List, undated; Series 7 (Box 118, Folder 2)
  - William Andrews Clark Camp Andree Clark, undated; Series 7 (Box 118, Folder 3)
  - Art Collection of the Late United States, undated; Series 7 (Box 118, Folder 4)
  - Farrington WA Clark Aricles, undated; Series 7 (Box 118, Folder 5)
  - Farrington WA Clark Aricles, undated; Series 7 (Box 118, Folder 6)
  - Mann WA Clark Articles, undated; Series 7 (Box 118, Folder 7)
  - Farrell WA Clark Articles, undated; Series 7 (Box 118, Folder 8)
  - Rodda, Young, undated; Series 7 (Box 118, Folder 9)
  - WA Clark Newspaperr Articles, undated; Series 7 (Box 118, Folder 10)
  - William Andrews Clark Articles and Bibliography, undated; Series 7 (Box 118, Folder 11)
  - Salon Dore- Articles on Sen. Clark and his NY residence, undated; Series 7 (Box 118, Folder 12)
  - William Andrews Clark 5th Avenue House, undated; Series 7 (Box 118, Folder 13)
  - Clark Residence, Petit Salon, undated; Series 7 (Box 118, Folder 14)
  - Clark Mansion Photography, undated; Series 7 (Box 118, Folder 15)
  - Clark Mansion: Raphael Collin, undated; Series 7 (Box 118, Folder 16)
  - Photo Album, undated; Series 7 (Box 118, Folder 17)
  - Loose wall labels, undated; Series 7
  - Loose wall labels, undated; Series 7
  - Working Draft Historic Structures Report Corcoran Gallery of Art Washington, DC, 1996 September; Series 7 (Box 119, Item 3)
  - The Salon Dore from the Hotel de Clermont by Edith Hutchinson Brewster, undated; Series 7 (Box 119, Item 4)
  - Clark Decorative Arts Furniture 26.795 Stone Mantel, undated; Series 7 (Box 119, Folder 5)
  - Moses P. Rice of William Wilson Corcoran in his parlor, undated; Series 7 (Box 119, Folder 6)
  - Association of Art Museum Directors - miscellaneous papers, circa 1938-1941; Series 7 (Box 119, Folder 7)
  - Association of Art Museum Directors - Abbott, Gene, circa 1938-1941; Series 7 (Box 119, Folder 8)
  - Association of Art Museum Directors - Austin, A.E., circa 1938-1941; Series 7 (Box 119, Folder 9)
  - Association of Art Museum Directors - Baldwin, Martin, circa 1938-1941; Series 7 (Box 119, Folder 10)
  - Association of Art Museum Directors - Bliss, Hon. Robert Woods, circa 1938-1941; Series 7 (Box 119, Folder 11)
  - Association of Art Museum Directors - Bloom, circa 1938-1941; Series 7 (Box 119, Folder 12)
  - Association of Art Museum Directors - Burroughs, Clyde H., circa 1938-1941; Series 7 (Box 119, Folder 13)
  - Association of Art Museum Directors - Carnegie Corporation, circa 1938-1941; Series 7 (Box 119, Folder 14)
  - Association of Art Museum Directors - Carter, Morris, circa 1938-1941; Series 7 (Box 119, Folder 15)
  - Association of Art Museum Directors - Clapp, Dr. Frederick Mortimer, circa 1938-1941; Series 7 (Box 119, Folder 16)
  - Association of Art Museum Directors - Currelly, C.J., circa 1938-1941; Series 7 (Box 119, Folder 17)
  - Association of Art Museum Directors - Edgell, G.H., circa 1938-1941; Series 7 (Box 119, Folder 18)
  - Association of Art Museum Directors - Finley, David E., circa 1938-1941; Series 7 (Box 119, Folder 19)
  - Association of Art Museum Directors - Gardner, Paul, circa 1938-1941; Series 7 (Box 119, Folder 20)
  - Association of Art Museum Directors - Godwin, Blake More, circa 1938-1941; Series 7 (Box 119, Folder 21)
  - Association of Art Museum Directors - Kent, H.W., circa 1938-1941; Series 7 (Box 119, Folder 22)
  - Association of Art Museum Directors - Kimball, Fiske, circa 1938-1941; Series 7 (Box 119, Folder 23)
  - Association of Art Museum Directors - MacLeod, J. Arthur, circa 1938-1941; Series 7 (Box 119, Folder 24)
  - Association of Art Museum Directors - Meeks, Everett V., circa 1938-1941; Series 7 (Box 119, Folder 25)
  - Association of Art Museum Directors - Mellon, Hon. A.W., circa 1938-1941; Series 7 (Box 119, Folder 26)
  - Association of Art Museum Directors - Millikien, Wm. M., circa 1938-1941; Series 7 (Box 119, Folder 27)
  - Association of Art Museum Directors - O'Connor, John, Jr., circa 1938-1941; Series 7 (Box 119, Folder 28)
  - Association of Art Museum Directors - Rogers, Meyric R., circa 1938-1941; Series 7 (Box 119, Folder 29)
  - Association of Art Museum Directors - Siple, Walter H., circa 1938-1941; Series 7 (Box 119, Folder 30)
  - Association of Art Museum Directors - Taylor, Francis Henry, circa 1938-1941; Series 7 (Box 119, Folder 31)
  - Association of Art Museum Directors - Winlock, H.E., circa 1938-1941; Series 7 (Box 119, Folder 32)
  - Association of Art Museum Directors - Youtz, Philip N., circa 1938-1941; Series 7 (Box 119, Folder 33)
  - Air Raid Precautions in Museums Picture Galleries and Libraries, printed by the Order of the Trustees The British Museum, 1939; Series 7 (Box 119, Folder 34)
  - Minutes of a Special Meeting of the Association of Museum Directors on the Problems of Protection and Defense held at The Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1941 December 20-21; Series 7 (Box 119, Folders 35-37)
  - NGA Transfer Sheets, undated; Series 7 (Box 120, Folder 1)
  - David, Gene Gene Davis 1982 Rotunda Mural Acrylic Ferris Wheel, Series 7 (Box 120, Folder 2)
  - Clark Devorative Arts Andirons 26.761 to 26.762 [Multiple Objects], undated; Series 7 (Box 120, Folder 3)
  - Clark Decorative Arts Stain Glass Windows 26.794 Window, undated; Series 7 (Box 120, Folder 4)
  - Francisci, Anthony de 35.2 Creation, undated; Series 7 (Box 120, Folder 5)
  - Boucher, After 26.743, 26.744 Cupid and Psyche, undated; Series 7 (Box 120, Folder 6)
  - Boucher, After 26.744 Psyche, undated; Series 7 (Box 120, Folder 7)
  - Scholer 1998.52.17 Pin Tails, undated; Series 7 (Box 120, Folder 8)
  - Laessle, Albert 41.70, undated; Series 7 (Box 120, Folder 9)
  - UA - Bryant Bauman UA 1002.1,+4, undated; Series 7 (Box 120, Folder 10)
  - King, Samuel L.55.2 Jonathan Jackson, undated; Series 7 (Box 120, Folder 11)
  - Shecter, Mark L.66.5 Abstraction 1,000, undated; Series 7 (Box 120, Folder 12)
  - Virgi McMahan and Robert Laible Collection General, undated; Series 7 (Box 120, Folder 13)
  - Ezekiel, Moses 82.8 Project for Relief Sculpture, undated; Series 7 (Box 120, Folder 14)
  - Clark Decorative Arts Rugs ARS/Official, undated; Series 7 (Box 120, Folder 15)
  - William A.Clark Collection Rugs- General, undated; Series 7 (Box 120, Folder 16)
  - Clark Decorative Arts Rugs Confidential, undated; Series 7 (Box 120, Folder 17)
  - Clark Decorative Arts Rugs Correspondence, undated; Series 7 (Box 120, Folder 18)
  - Clark Decorative Arts Rugs Exhibitions and Exhibition Catalogs, undated; Series 7 (Box 120, Folder 19)
  - Clark Decorative Arts Rugs Outgoing Loans, undated; Series 7 (Box 120, Folder 20)
  - Clark Decorative Arts Rugs References, undated; Series 7 (Box 120, Folder 21)
  - Clark Decorative Arts Rugs Rights and Reproductions, undated; Series 7 (Box 120, Folder 22)
  - Georgia O'Keeffe Photo, undated; Series 7 (Box 120, Folder 23)
  - Corcoran Publications, undated; Series 7 (Box 120, Folder 24)
  - Postcards, undated; Series 7 (Box 120, Folder 25)
  - Marble Sample Console Table, undated; Series 7 (Box 120, Folder 26)
  - Muybridge Left Corcoran 1997 VA 0061-0423, undated; Series 7 (Box 120, Folder 27)
  - Bryant Gift - Chandelier, Side Table, Desk - All Deaccessioned + sold at Southeby's Weschler's UA 1004.1-3, undated; Series 7 (Box 120, Folder 28)
  - 2 Paintings Donated to Winterthur: 2011-Lelia Caetani, Landscape Jermoneta 2014-Portrait of Mabel L. Williams, undated; Series 7 (Box 120, Folder 29)
  - Norment bequest: 3 paintings sold, 1980+1982 Gaugin, (Fantin-Latour, and Utrillo), undated; Series 7 (Box 120, Folder 30)
  - Cassatt, Mary Stevenson 07.25.a, undated; Series 7 (Box 120, Folder 31)
  - 86.1, undated; Series 7 (Box 120, Folder 32)
  - Durand, A.B. 83.4, undated; Series 7 (Box 120, Folder 33)
  - 26A22, undated; Series 7 (Box 120, Folder 34)
  - Healy, George Peter Alexander 88.7 Robert M McLean, undated; Series 7 (Box 120, Folder 35)
  - Lafean, Richard 64.4, undated; Series 7 (Box 120, Folder 36)
  - Multhauf, Mary 59.60 Stoneware Bowl, undated; Series 7 (Box 120, Folder 37)
  - Neri, Manuel 1997.26.1 to 1997.26.138, undated; Series 7 (Box 120, Folder 38)
  - LeClerc, Jerome (attributed) 44.15, undated; Series 7 (Box 120, Folder 39)
  - Robbe, Louis "Landscape", undated; Series 7 (Box 120, Folder 40)
  - Schoor, Lucas 44.13.14-16 Three Flemish Tapestries, undated; Series 7 (Box 120, Folder 41)
  - Wyon, J.S. & A.B. 83.12 Seal of the Confederate States of America, undated; Series 7 (Box 120, Folder 42)
  - SWA card file: index to SWA exhibitions, undated; Series 7 (Box 121)
  - Card files to artists in the Washington Area exhibition, undated; Series 7 (Box 122)
  - Slide Presentation on Corcoran Gallery of Art, 1983 April; Series 7 (Box 123, Box 1)
  - Maryland print quality awards competition plaque - catalogs, 1981; Series 7 (Box 123, Item 2)
  - Maryland print quality awards competition plaque - art reproduction, 1981; Series 7 (Box 123, Item 3)
  - Unidentified nail and building materials, undated; Series 7 (Box 123, Box 4)
  - Collection plaques Miss Mary E. Maxwell, undated; Series 7 (Box 123, Item 5-6)
  - Black binder with newspaper and magazine clippings, 1990; Series 7 (Box 124, Item 1)
  - Magazine, Washington Project for the Arts: From the Potomac to the Anacostia, 1989; Series 7 (Box 124, Folders 2-9)
  - Magazine, Washington Review volume 20 number 1, 1994 June/July; Series 7 (Box 124, Folders 10-13)
  - Magazine, Washington Project for the Arts: From the Potomac to the Anacostia, 1989; Series 7 (Box 124, Folders 14-17)
  - WPA Celebrating More Than A Decade, 1986; Series 7 (Box 124, Folders 18-19)
  - Deed and Charter of the Corcoran Gallery of Art, 1869; Series 7 (Box 127, Item 1)
  - Deed, Charter, By-Laws, List of Trustees- the Corcoran Gallery of Art, Washington DC-, 1929; Series 7 (Box 127, Item 2)
  - The Library of Congress- the Statutes at Large and Proclamations of the United States of America from December 1869 to March 1\871 Volume XVI- photocopies of the spine, title page, and page 139, 1869-1871; Series 7 (Box 127, Item 3)
  - Centerbook Architects and Planners Essex, Connecticut, undated; Series 7 (Box 127, Item 4)
  - Washington Convention Center Art Program- Master Plan, 2001 May 24; Series 7 (Box 127, Item 5)
  - Graphics for Teaching, Magazines, Advertisements, undated; Series 7 (Box 127, Item 6)
  - Libeskind Press, undated; Series 7 (Box 127, Item 7)
  - Windsor Station Canadian Pacific Limited, undated; Series 7 (Box 127, Item 8)
  - F8 Cotman Deluxe Watercolor Book, undated; Series 7 (Box 127, Item 9)
  - Balma, undated; Series 7 (Box 127, Item 10)
  - Large Book of Exhibition Photos, undated; Series 7 (Box 128, Item 1)
  - The Corcoran Museum of Art School of Art Sketches Part I- Santiago Calatrava Valls, 1999 June; Series 7 (Box 128, Item 2)
  - The Corcoran Museum of Art School of Art Sketches Part II- Santiago Calatrava Valls, 1999 June; Series 7 (Box 128, Item 3)
  - The Corcoran Museum of Art School of Art Sketches Part III- Santiago Calatrava Valls, 1999 June; Series 7 (Box 128, Item 4)
  - The Corcoran Museum of Art School of Art Sketches Part IV- Santiago Calatrava Valls, 1999 June; Series 7 (Box 128, Item 5)
  - The Corcoran Museum of Art School of Art Sketches Part V- Santiago Calatrava Valls, 1999 June; Series 7 (Box 128, Item 6)
- Corcoran Library administrative files, Series 8
  - Library Accession The Corcoran School of Art, 1973-1976; Series 8 (Box 125, Folder 1)
  - Corcoran School of Art Cash Library, undated; Series 8 (Box 125, Folder 2)
  - Accessions, 1964-1973; Series 8 (Box 125, Folder 3)
  - Book Sale Expenses, undated; Series 8 (Box 125, Folder 4)
  - Transmittal Forms, undated; Series 8 (Box 125, Folder 5)
  - Book Sale/Book Shops, undated; Series 8 (Box 125, Folder 6)
  - Alumni Benefit for the Library, 1996 March; Series 8 (Box 125, Folder 7)
  - Paxton Van Lines Office Moving Division, undated; Series 8 (Box 125, Folder 8)
  - Furniture Stuff, undated; Series 8 (Box 125, Folder 9)
  - Shelving Installers & Shelving, undated; Series 8 (Box 125, Folder 10)
  - Graph Paper, undated; Series 8 (Box 125, Folder 11)
  - Library Planning, undated; Series 8 (Box 125, Folder 12)
  - Library Renovation/Move, undated; Series 8 (Box 125, Folder 13)
  - Floor Plans, undated; Series 8 (Box 125, Folder 14)
  - Architects' Survey, 1998 April; Series 8 (Box 125, Folder 15)
  - Gaylord, undated; Series 8 (Box 125, Folder 16)
  - Change of Address, undated; Series 8 (Box 125, Folder 17)
  - Name Change, undated; Series 8 (Box 125, Folder 18)
  - Automation Notes, 1998; Series 8 (Box 125, Folder 19)
  - Research & Correspondence, 1995-1996; Series 8 (Box 125, Folder 20)
  - General Computer Infro Computerization Workshop, 1994; Series 8 (Box 125, Folder 21)
  - Inventory, undated; Series 8 (Box 125, Folder 22)
  - Barcodes Electronic Services, undated; Series 8 (Box 125, Folder 23)
  - AP Development, undated; Series 8 (Box 125, Folder 24)
  - Cost Figures, undated; Series 8 (Box 125, Folder 25)
  - Presentation, undated; Series 8 (Box 125, Folder 26)
  - Other DT Libraries, plus comments from the other libraries about other products, undated; Series 8 (Box 125, Folder 27)
  - Microcomputer, undated; Series 8 (Box 125, Folder 28)
  - Stat Sheets- Accrediation, undated; Series 8 (Box 125, Folder 29)
  - CHE Guidebooks, undated; Series 8 (Box 125, Folder 30)
  - Midstates Periodic Review Report, 1996 March; Series 8 (Box 125, Folder 31)
  - Corcoran Gallery 5-Year Plan, 1993 November; Series 8 (Box 125, Folder 32)
  - Library Mission Statement, 1992; Series 8 (Box 125, Folder 33)
  - Self-Study - Library Sections, 1990 September; Series 8 (Box 125, Folder 34)
  - Misc. Internal Reports, etc. RE: Needed Improvements, undated; Series 8 (Box 125, Folder 35)
  - Library Subcommittee, undated; Series 8 (Box 125, Folder 36)
  - Linda Hales Donation, undated; Series 8 (Box 126, Folder 1)
  - Individual Gifts, 2003; Series 8 (Box 126, Folder 2)
  - Individual Gifts, 2000; Series 8 (Box 126, Folder 3)
  - Individual Gifts, 1999; Series 8 (Box 126, Folder 4)
  - Individual Gifts, 1998; Series 8 (Box 126, Folder 5)
  - Zeuxis Neves Donation, undated; Series 8 (Box 126, Folder 6)
  - Tibbs Collection, undated; Series 8 (Box 126, Folder 7)
  - Tibbs Collection, undated; Series 8 (Box 126, Folder 8)
  - Tibbs (in Library Storage Closet and Pat's office), undated; Series 8 (Box 126, Folder 9)
  - Hirshhorn Books (in P&D office), undated; Series 8 (Box 126, Folder 10)
  - Barbara Smith Coleman Donation, 2003; Series 8 (Box 126, Folder 11)
  - Blair, Warren E., undated; Series 8 (Box 126, Folder 12)
  - Grey Carter Donation, undated; Series 8 (Box 126, Folder 13)
  - Individual Gifts, 2001; Series 8 (Box 126, Folder 14)
  - Individual Gift Acknowledgements, 1997; Series 8 (Box 126, Folder 15)
  - Miscellaneous One-Time Donors, undated; Series 8 (Box 126, Folder 16)
  - Beck, undated; Series 8 (Box 126, Folder 17)
  - Bellucci, undated; Series 8 (Box 126, Folder 18)
  - Cowart, undated; Series 8 (Box 126, Folder 19)
  - Fry, undated; Series 8 (Box 126, Folder 20)
  - Getlein, undated; Series 8 (Box 126, Folder 21)
  - Golden, James, undated; Series 8 (Box 126, Folder 22)
  - Kinney, undated; Series 8 (Box 126, Folder 23)
  - McWilliams, undated; Series 8 (Box 126, Folder 24)
  - Mann, Jonathan S., undated; Series 8 (Box 126, Folder 25)
  - Newman, undated; Series 8 (Box 126, Folder 26)
  - Pickering, undated; Series 8 (Box 126, Folder 27)
  - Reyes, Brigitte, undated; Series 8 (Box 126, Folder 28)
  - Rockwood, undated; Series 8 (Box 126, Folder 29)
  - Roth, Edith Brill, undated; Series 8 (Box 126, Folder 30)
  - Sarnoff, undated; Series 8 (Box 126, Folder 31)
  - Solinger, undated; Series 8 (Box 126, Folder 32)
  - Szabo, undated; Series 8 (Box 126, Folder 33)
  - Thornton, undated; Series 8 (Box 126, Folder 34)
  - Weige, undated; Series 8 (Box 126, Folder 35)
  - Welt, undated; Series 8 (Box 126, Folder 36)
  - Wenner, undated; Series 8 (Box 126, Folder 37)
  - Memorandum for P.O. Price Adjustment, undated; Series 8 (Box 126, Folder 38)
  - Museum Exchange, 2003; Series 8 (Box 126, Folder 39)
  - Museum Exchange, 2002; Series 8 (Box 126, Folder 40)
  - Museum Exchange, 2001; Series 8 (Box 126, Folder 41)
  - Museum Exchange, 2000; Series 8 (Box 126, Folder 42)
  - Museum Exchange, 1999; Series 8 (Box 126, Folder 43)
  - Museum Exchange Acknowledgements, 1998; Series 8 (Box 126, Folder 44)
  - Museum Exchange Acknowledgements, 1997; Series 8 (Box 126, Folder 45)
  - Exchange Activity, 1996; Series 8 (Box 126, Folder 46)
  - Exchange Activity, 1995; Series 8 (Box 126, Folder 47)
  - Catalogues Sent Out, 1986-1990; Series 8 (Box 126, Folder 48)
  - Annual Acquisition Statistics, undated; Series 8 (Box 126, Folder 49)
  - Annual Circulation Statistics, undated; Series 8 (Box 126, Folder 50)
  - AV Statistics, undated; Series 8 (Box 126, Folder 51)
  - Annual Patron Statistics, undated; Series 8 (Box 126, Folder 52)
  - Book Counts, undated; Series 8 (Box 126, Folder 53)
  - Book Recataloged, undated; Series 8 (Box 126, Folder 54)
  - Visitation Stats, 1994 November-December; Series 8 (Box 126, Folder 55)